

Zunayed Shahriar

Full-Stack Software Developer

+88 01675099152

in zunayeds

About Me_

Enthusiastic software developer with more than 6 years of experience working in the computer software industry who doesn't get inner peace until a challenging problem is solved. I wish to work with a diverse group of people to build great software solutions and won't hesitate to learn new technologies regardless of my comfort zone.

Technical Skills _

Languages C# • TypeScript • JavaScript • SQL • C++

Technologies .NET Framework • .NET • Entity Framework Core • Xamarin Forms • Angular • Git

Work Experience

Senior Full Stack Developer

MPower Technology Solutions Sdn. Bhd. 2

May 2022 - Present

Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia (Remote)

- Role: Full Stack Software Developer

- Responsibilities: Application development, Database design, REST API development, UI design, performance tuning.

- Backend Technologies: .NET Core, Entity Framework Core, .NET Framework, WinForms, VB.NET

- Frontend Technologies: Angular, AngularJS

- SQL: SQL Server

- Reporting: SQL Server Reporting Services

- Domain: Manufacturing

- Cloud: Azure

- Source Control: Git

Software Engineer

Relisource Technologies Limited 2

Jun 2021 – Apr 2022

- Role: Full Stack Software Developer

Dhaka, Bangladesh (Remote)

- Responsibilities: Application development and deployment, UI design, performance tuning, Team-leading.
- Backend Technologies: .NET Core, Entity Framework Core, WinForms, WCF

- Frontend Technologies: Angular, AngularJS

SQL: SQL Server

- Mobile App Technologies: Xamarin Forms

- Domain: Healthcare (Clinical Trial Management)

- Cloud: Azure

- Source Control: Git

Software Developer

Softech Limited 2

Feb 2020 – Jun 2021

Dhaka, Bangladesh (Remote)

- Role: Full Stack Software Developer

 Responsibilities: System Architecture design, application development and deployment, Database design, UI design, capture client requirement, Team-leading.

- Backend Technologies: .NET Core, Entity Framework Core, WinForms, WCF

- Frontend Technologies: Angular

SQL: SQL ServerSource Control: Git

- Domain: Partner Management, Sales Management

- Projects:

- Red Express: A Sales Order Management System for Robi Axiata Limited.
- **B-Trac Partner Portal:** A Sales Tracking System with Partner Management and Warranty Tracking feature for B-Trac Technologies Limited.

Programmer Analyst

Computer Ease Limited 2

Jan 2017 - Feb 2020 Dhaka, Bangladesh

Role: Full Stack Software Developer

Responsibilities: Application development and deployment, Database management, UI design, Report design, Mobile App development, Query optimization, REST API development, Windows Service development, mentor junior developers, capture client requirements and conduct client-end UAT sessions.

- Backend Technologies: .NET Framework, .NET Core, WinForms, WCF

Frontend Technologies: .NET MVC 5, Silverlight, Angular

- SQL: SQL Server

- Reporting: Telerik Reports

- Mobile App Technologies: Xamarin Forms

- Source Control: SVN

Domain: Telecom, Distributed Sales Management

- Robi Sales Tracking System (STS): A Sales Tracking Management System for Robi Axiata Limited.
- Robi Distributor Registration Portal: A Distributor Registration System for Robi Axiata Limited.
- Robi Distributor App: An Android app for Distributors Sales Tracking System for Robi Axiata Limited.
- Robi Retailer Registration Portal: A Retailer Registration system for Robi Axiata Limited.

Intern

Grameen Communications <a>C

Feb 2016 - Dec 2016 Dhaka, Bangladesh

- Role: Intern, Software Developer

- Responsibilities: Application development, Mobile App development, capture client requirements.

- Backend Technologies: .NET Framework

- Frontend Technologies: .NET MVC 5, ASP.NET WebForms

- SQL: SQL Server

Reporting: Crystal Reports

- Mobile App Technologies: Android Native, Windows Phone Native, JAVA MIDP

Source Control: TFS

- Domain: Project Management (Microcredit)

Projects:

- Nobin Udyokta Project Management System (NUPMS): A management system based on an idea which founded by Noble literate Prof. Dr. Muhammad Yunus to fund new entrepreneurs to jump-start their business.
- **gNUm App:** A mobile app to track daily business status of a funded new entrepreneur.

Education_

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

Southeast University [2]

Jan 2012 - Dec 2016 Dhaka, Bangladesh

- Represented University in 6 National Onsite Programming Contests including ACM ICPC 2016 Asia Regional Dhaka Site.
- Became Champion in Southeast University Intra Individual Programming Contest in Fall 2015.
- Organized Southeast University Division 2 Programming Contest Championship alongside Southeast University Programming Contest Arena Members in 2016.
- Published journal on the topic of University Timetable Generator Using Tabu Search on Journal of Computer and Communications, Vol.4 No.16, December 2016.

Problem Solving Platform Profile ___



Trained Beginner level programming contestants for one year.











